cookneasy.com 2003-06-04

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Overview**

**The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of[www.jdworld.net](http://www.jdworld.net/) (including [cookneasy.com](http://www.cookneasy.com/), [varketmarket.com](http://www.varketmarket.com/), [certnerd.com](http://www.certnerd.com/), [bannedintheus.com](http://www.bannedintheus.com/), [coffeewithcream.com](http://www.coffeewithcream.com/)) and apply generally to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites whose specific privacy policies are available from our Privacy pages. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.**

As described below, as part of the normal operation of our services, your information is collected by us, disclosed to third parties and used by third parties and us. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about Jdworld.net Network practices so that you can make informed decisions. All of our subsidiaries and joint ventures operate under similar privacy practices as described in this Privacy Policy and, subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the global Jdworld Network community.

By accepting the Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy is effective on April 20th, 2002 for new visitors and users. There has been no prior amendments to this privacy policy.

  1. **A Special Note About Children.**  
Children are not eligible to use our services and we ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use our service only in conjunction with your parents or guardians.
  2. **Information We Collect.**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier.

In general, you can browse our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, billing information, shipping information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout our site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, such as, but not limited to: if you are registering using an email account at a free email service, or registering for an email account.

We do not automatically track certain information when you visit our sites. We do not use data collection devices such as "cookies".

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of our site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you choose to post messages in our chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback for other users, we will not collect that information you provide to us. However; we will monitor for misuse and/or for chat etiquette.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

If you register for services on the Jdworld.net Network on another web site or use a web site providing a service for the Jdworld.net Network and Affiliates or a web site that helps facilitate your activity on our sites, that web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to us.

  3. **Our Use of Your Information.**  
We use your information to facilitate the services you request. We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases.

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize our site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications on the registration pages. You may make changes to your notification preferences at any time, or you may email us to do so.

  4. **Our Disclosure of Your Information.**  
Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our site. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we **do not** sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

**Advertisers.** We aggregate (gather up data across all user accounts) personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your name, email address, password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed to marketing advertisers ever. If you "right click" with your mouse on an ad on our site and select properties, you can see the URL for the advertiser that serves that ad.

**Internal Service Providers.** We may use internal service providers to facilitate our services (e.g., search, discussion boards, surveys) and therefore we may provide some of your personally identifiable information directly to them. In some instances, the internal service provider may collect information directly from you (such as the situation where we ask a internal service provider to conduct a survey for us). In these cases, you will be notified of the involvement of the internal service provider, and all information disclosures you make will be strictly optional. In all cases, these internal service providers' use of information we supply them is restricted by confidentiality agreements. If you provide additional information to an internal service provider directly, then their use of your information is governed by their applicable privacy policy.

**Legal Requests.** Jdworld.net and its Affiliates cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.  Additionally, Jdworld.net and its Affiliates reserves the right (and you authorize us) to communicate any information about you (including, but not limited to your policy violations), to other users, law enforcement and other members as we in our sole discretion determine necessary or appropriate to maintain a level of trust and safety in our community and to enforce our User Agreement, Privacy Policy and any posted policies or rules applicable to services you use through our site.

Jdworld.net and its Affiliates and our users do not tolerate spam. Therefore, without limiting the foregoing, you are not licensed to add a user, to your mail list (email or physical mail) without their express consent after adequate disclosure. To report spam to Jdworld.net, please send an email to [admin@jdworld.net](mailto:admin@jdworld.net).

  7. **Control of Your Password.**  
You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your login password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.
  8. **Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information.**  
You can change your user Id, email address, contact information, shipping information and user preferences by sending an email to admin@jdworld.net. You must promptly update your information if it changes. Once posted, you may not be able to change or remove any public postings made on our site including our chat rooms or other message areas.

Upon your request, we will deactivate your account, contact information, shipping information, from our active databases to prevent your information from being shared with other users. To make this request, email to admin@jdworld.net. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible based on your account activity and in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law.

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

  9. **Security.**  
The Jdworld.net Network and Associates uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.
  10. **Conflict of Terms.**  
It is our goal to make our privacy practices easy to understand. We have created easy-to-read summaries, privacy principles, a privacy chart and, are working on privacy enhancing technology to help summarize our full privacy policy. If you have questions about any part of this summary or if you would like more detailed information, we encourage you to send us an email to [admin@jdworld.net](mailto:admin@jdworld.net)
  11. **Notice.**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amend terms on our site. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on our site. In addition, we will notify you in accordance with your notification preferences.
